businessofsuccess.com 2008-09-21

# Privacy Policy - Business of Success

**B.O.S. Online Privacy Notice**  
(Updated - November 11, 2004)

**Our Commitment To Privacy**

At B.O.S., we are committed to protecting your privacy online. Our pledge is to safeguard any personal information that you provide us, and to make every reasonable effort to use this information only as you choose. We at B.O.S. are taking a leadership role in assisting our customers and other businesses in understanding the importance of using your personal information appropriately.

**Scope of This Notice**

The goal of this Privacy Notice is to advise you of the online privacy practices of B.O.S. and to describe the choices you have about the way the information collected on this site is used. It also applies to consumer digital registration cards. For information about other offline data collections, use the contact information noted below.

**PLEASE NOTE:**

  * **This statement does not apply to our commercial customers.**
  * **If when you provide your personal information you indicate your residence as outside the U.S., you may be offered a privacy notice which is specific to your country of residence. In such case, B.O.S. is operating this site for itself as well as a service provider for its global affiliates.**
  * **On our co-branded sites (such as those sites where B.O.S. has presented content together with one of our retail partners) a privacy notice unique to that site will be presented.**
  * **Private sites (such as those only available to dealers and distributors) and sites created for our employees (or prospective employees) may also have privacy notices unique to those sites.**

**Collecting Your Personal Information**

This Online Privacy Notice covers the collection and use of personal information. Personal Information is data that reasonably can be used to identify or describe an individual.

B.O.S. collects personal information online when:

  * you register to become a member of B.O.S..com or another B.O.S. service
  * you make online purchases
  * you submit questions or comments to us
  * you request information or materials
  * you request warranty or post-warranty service and support for a B.O.S. product
  * you register products online
  * you participate in online surveys
  * you participate in online promotions, premiums, sweepstakes or contests
  * you request we send information to your friends, family and colleagues

The type of information collected may include name, address, phone number, Social Security or other tax identification number, billing and delivery information, e-mail address, gift recipient information, credit card information and other demographic information.

**Using Your Information**

B.O.S. uses the personal information you provide to:

  * register you in programs
  * create and maintain accounts
  * process, fulfill, and follow up on orders
  * answer your e-mail
  * send information you request
  * send friends, families and colleagues information on your behalf
  * send surveys
  * register products

We also use this personal information to provide you with information related to your account, the products or services you purchased from us, to better understand your needs and interests, to improve our service and to personalize communications.

**Sharing Your Personal Information**

B.O.S. will not sell, rent, or trade the personal information you provide online. We do share your personal information with certain B.O.S. business affiliates.

B.O.S. may disclose personal information to third parties without your consent for any of the following reasons: to comply with any law, regulation or court order, to cooperate with Government investigations, to help prevent fraud or to enforce or protect the rights of B.O.S. or its subsidiaries.

B.O.S. reserves the right to transfer your personal information in connection with the sale or transfer of all or a portion of our business or assets. If the business is sold or transferred, B.O.S. will give you an opportunity to tell us not to transfer your personal information. In some cases, this may mean that the new organization will not be able to continue providing to you the services or products that B.O.S. provided.

**Your Choices about Receiving E-mail**

B.O.S. may send you e-mail about your orders or your account and in response to your questions. B.O.S. and its subsidiaries may also send you e-mail with information and/or special offers about products and services that may be of interest to you, unless you indicate you do not want to receive them.

We will give you an opportunity to let us know your preference regarding the receiving of promotional e-mail when you register for a service, when you provide us with your personal information, or when we send you e-mail. If you choose not to accept this promotional e-mail, you may not receive special offers that may be of value to you. This option applies to promotional e-mail only, as we may find it necessary to send you e-mail relating to your account or order.

Promotional e-mail that you receive from B.O.S. will tell you how to decline receiving future promotional e-mail.

**Information Collected through Use of Cookies and Other Technologie** s

B.O.S. automatically receives and records data on our servers from visitor browsers including computer IP (Internet Protocol) addresses and other information through the use of cookies. This information is collected about thousands of site visits and analyzed as a whole. This analysis looks for trends among many visitors to B.O.S. or other B.O.S. sites, and determines which parts of the site are accessed most frequently and what information visitors find most valuable.

We may also collect and record information about what you viewed on our Web site. We may use this type of information and combine it with your personal information to help customize our future interactions with you. In doing so, we hope to provide better service to you by tailoring our communications to match your interests- to give you more of what you want and less of what you don't want.

**Protecting Your Information**

B.O.S. implements a variety of administrative, managerial, and technical security measures to help protect your personal information. B.O.S. has Internal Control Standards which relate specifically to the handling of personal information. These include certain controls to help safeguard the information we collect online.

B.O.S. employees are trained to understand and comply with these controls and we communicate our privacy policy, practices and guidelines to our employees. However, while we strive to protect your personal information, you must also take steps to protect your information. We urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal information while you are on the Internet.

**Communities**

Some of our sites may enable you to participate in public services such as discussion boards, chats, and live events. Please use discretion when posting personal information about yourself when using these services. Be aware that when you disclose personal information at these sites, such as your name, member name, e-mail address, etc., the information may be collected and used by others to send unsolicited e-mail. The services are open to the public, and what you post there can be seen by anyone and is not protected. B.O.S. cannot control the comments that you may receive while you participate in these services. You may find other people's comments to be offensive, harmful or inaccurate.

**Children's Privacy**

Protecting the online privacy of children is especially important, and those under the age of 13 are protected by federal law. For that reason, B.O.S. does not knowingly permit children under the age of 13 to become registered members of our sites, or to buy goods and services on our sites, without verifiable parental consent. B.O.S. does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information about children under 13, except with their parent's express consent.

If we ever include children under the age of 13 as part of our intended site audience, those specific web pages will, in accordance with the provisions of the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), be clearly identified and provide an explicit privacy notice; and we will provide processes to obtain parental approval, provide access to information and allow parents to request removal of their children's personal information.

B.O.S. encourages parents and guardians to spend time with their children online and to participate in their interactive activities and interests.

**Outside Links**

Some B.O.S. Web sites contain links to and from other Web sites and B.O.S. is not responsible for the privacy practices of those Web sites. B.O.S. encourages you to ascertain the privacy practices of those Web sites.

**Keeping Your Information Accurate**

If you are a registered member of B.O.S., you can review and update your member profile using your user name and password. You also have the option of sending an e-mail to the address noted in the "How to Reach Us" section below to request a change to your information or a copy of the personal information we have collected about you online. There may be a nominal charge for information requested. We will make every reasonable effort to make sure your requests are met. To protect your privacy, proof of identity is required.

**How to Reach Us**

If you have questions or concerns about your privacy when using a B.O.S. Web site, please contact us by e-mail:  [privacy@businessofsuccess.com](mailto:privacy@businessofsuccess.com) or by mail at:

Business of Success  
Online Privacy Office  
3388 Via Lido, Second Floor  
Newport Beach, CA 92677

B.O.S.'s Online Privacy Office will work with you to resolve any concerns you have about this policy.

**Changes to this Privacy Notice**

B.O.S. reserves the right to modify this privacy notice from time to time, by posting a prominent announcement on this page or, in the event of a material change, by notifying by e-mail all customers whose personal information we have retained.

This Privacy Notice was last amended on 11/11/04.

Who are B.O.S.'s "business affiliates"?

  * **B.O.S.'s subsidiaries and joint ventures**

A subsidiary or a joint venture is an organization in which B.O.S. owns at least a 50% interest. If B.O.S. shares your information with a subsidiary or joint venture partner, B.O.S. will direct them that they may not transfer your information to another party for marketing purposes or use your information contrary to your expressed choices. If you have indicated that you do not want to receive any marketing information from B.O.S., we will not share your information with our subsidiary or joint venture partner for their marketing purposes.

  * **Companies who assist B.O.S. to complete or follow-up on your order**

B.O.S. may share your personal information, as necessary, with companies who contract with B.O.S. to fulfill and/or ship an order, an award, or rebate; conduct surveys; assist in the processing of our accounts and managing our systems; collect payments; facilitate e-mail subscriptions; or to provide a product or service you have requested. We require these companies to use the shared information only for these limited purposes, and not to transfer the information to another party.

What are "cookies" and how does B.O.S. use them?

Cookies are small pieces of information stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive, at a web site's request. B.O.S. cookies do not contain any personal information and are used for these reasons: (1) we use cookies to keep track of temporary information. For example, cookies allow us to keep track of the pictures you upload and download; (2) to register you in programs, such as www.businessofsuccess.com Membership. Cookies allow us to remember you when you login to the places on our site which require Membership; (3) to remember your country and language preferences; (4) to help us understand the size of our audience and traffic patterns; (5) to manage and present site information and the pictures displayed on your computer, and (6) to deliver information specific to your interests.
